http://www.fetishnetwork.com/records/privacy_policy.html

M3Nyc
Privacy Policy
THIS IS AN ADULTS ONLY SERVICE
We will suspend or terminate any accounts
which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18)
years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view
the Sites; additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to
the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or
with respect to such person.
Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety
Your name, physical address, phone number and
password are considered confidential. However, all information you
provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to
comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the
court system.
Information We Collect From You
During sign up we require that you provide us with certain information
which may include Account Data (i.e., your name, physical address, email
address, phone number, username, and password), Financial Data (i.e.,
credit card/billing information) along with "Demographic Information".
Demographic Information may include IP address(es), referring website
information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding
search history, browsing history, registration and user history.
How is this Information Used?
Financial Data will only be shared with third party processors as
necessary to initiate and complete any orders placed by your account.
We may use "cookies" and Demographic Information to better your
experience on the Site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the
Sites according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you
based on such Demographic Information. Aggregate, non-individual
membership Demographic Information may be shared with third parties with
whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products
or services we believe you may be interested in.
We may also share the aggregate Demographic Information with third
parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers
and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and
the Sites.
Emails From Us and use of Your Email Address
Your email address will be used by us to contact you when we have
special offers or other information to provide you. Such information may
include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information
relating to your account and other information related to your
subscription to the Sites. We may send you emails prior to and after you
have terminated your membership to our service until such time as you
advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you
no longer wish to receive email from us and/or from third parties with
whom we have a direct or indirect relationship. We may share your email
address with other third parties, with whom we have a direct or indirect
relationship with, for the purposes of sending you special
advertisements or promotions. If at any time you no longer wish to
receive emails from us or from such third parties please visit, you may
send us an email at
HYPERLINK "mailto:support@rknethelp.com"
support@fetishnetwork.com . We and our advertising partners fully comply
with the federal CAN-SPAM Act and as such all emails from us and our
advertising partners will always, among other required disclosures, have
a place for you to opt out of receipt of further email correspondence.
Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our
marketing partners without your consent. Please immediately report any emails you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purport to promote the Sites.
Advertisements
We utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our
services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we
or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or "action tags" to
measure advertising effectiveness on an "anonymous basis". Some emails
from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to the
Sites. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser's website, we
cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and
conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers' websites. If you
choose to make any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from
such companies, we may provide your information, including Financial
Data, to the advertiser as necessary to your request. Finally, we
cannot, and do not, make any representations about the privacy policies
or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our
service, whether through our website or emails, this is regardless of
whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all
of the Sites on such advertisers' website(s).
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We may change this privacy policy at any time. You agree that we are
under no duty to send you notice of such changes. Instead it is your
responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. No change
in the privacy policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it
is posted, unless the privacy policy has clear language indicating
otherwise.
Changes in the Ownership of the Sites
The Sites are a growing online service. As such, we may have the
occasion to buy or sell assets, including but not limited to merger,
dissolution, and transfer of ownership. Depending upon the nature of the
transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us
(including Financial Data and Account Information) with third parties,
as necessary to initiate, investigate or complete any such
transaction(s).
CONTACT
FetishWealth.com
